本字幕由「泉水渗透进字幕组」制作
听写：Whisper      翻译&时轴：yojoU      压制：FFmpeg
Is everyone bringing a treat for the Emmy party?
大家都带了点心去艾美奖派对吗
I made "How I Met Your Muffins".
我做了「松饼的浪漫史」
How I Met Your Mother《老爸老妈的浪漫史》
New Adventures of Old Krispies.
米酥新上路
The New Adventures of Old Christine《俏妈新上路》
Lost Carrots.
迷失胡萝卜
That's ham.
这是火腿
Or is it?
是吗
Who put a hundred bucks on Glee to win?
谁赌一百块《欢乐合唱团》得奖
You like Glee?
你喜欢《欢乐合唱团》吗
I like 200 bucks.
我喜欢钱
I'm only going to this party for you guys,
我只是为了你们才参加这个派对
and I don't subscribe to the ritual worship of self-indulgent narcissists
我不赞同对那些自我放纵的自恋狂进行仪式崇拜
making long-winded speeches about causes that only they possibly care about.
他们对那些只有他们才关心的事情发表长篇大论
阿布蒂  让她闭嘴
黄金时段艾美奖  由全新英菲尼迪QX56为您呈现
《废柴联盟》第二季将于9月23日周四在NBC首播
I can't wait for this Emmy party.
我等不及参加艾美奖派对了
Oh, let's play Emmy seat-filler.
我们来扮演艾美奖填座员吧
Seat-filler: 在颁奖典礼上负责填补空座的人
I'm leaving my seat at the Emmys.
我在艾美奖典礼上离开了座位
I'm filling your seat.
我来填你的空位
Oh seat-filler.
填座员来了
I'm gonna fill Annie's seat.
我来填安妮的位置
I'm filling Pierce's seat.
我来填皮尔斯的
I'm filling the seat of the angry dude from Nurse Jackie.
我来填《护士当家》里愤怒男的位置
Seat-filler.
填座员来也
What the hell are you doing here?
你在这搞什么鬼
Let's just say my wife did not leave me and
这么说吧  我老婆没有离开我
I have not been living in your car.
我也没一直住在你车里
Jeff, he's got a whole setup back there.
杰夫  他在后座有一整套装备
There's a toothbrush, an alarm clock, and
有牙刷  闹钟...
what's the coffee can for?
咖啡罐是干啥用的
Let's just say coffee.
喝咖啡
Oh, that's reassuring.
哦  那我真是放心了
黄金时段艾美奖  由全新英菲尼迪QX56为您呈现
《废柴联盟》第二季将于9月23日周四在NBC首播
Abed, we've been driving for hours.
阿布蒂  我们都开了好几个小时了
How much further?
还有多远
Up to you.
取决于你
How was it up to me?
我怎么决定
Where is your Emmy party?
你的艾美奖派对在哪里
It's here.
就在这
This is the Emmy party.
这就是艾美奖派对
Abed, you made us miss all the awards.
阿布蒂  你害我们错过了所有的奖项
Yeah, but by doing it, I give us the most important award of all.
虽然但是  我给我们颁了一个最重要的奖
Most Outstanding Friendship.
「最佳友谊奖」
Oh, this guy's adorable.
这家伙真可爱
Do not aww him.
别对他「噢」
He's a lunatic.
他是个疯子
You know what, Jeff?
你知道吗  杰夫
I think you need to take us home now.
我觉得你现在该带我们回家了
Ice cream first.
先吃冰淇淋
No, there's no way that I'm going to look like the bad guy in this.
没门  打死我都不能让我背黑锅
I wasted a whole evening picking you all up.
我浪费了一傍晚来接你们
I have been more than a...
我已经不止是个...
Playing him off.
让他闭麦
There's no way you're getting ice cream.
你们别想吃到冰淇淋
Ice cream.
冰淇淋
黄金时段艾美奖  由全新英菲尼迪QX56为您呈现
Ice cream! Ice cream! Ice cream!
冰淇淋 冰淇淋 冰淇淋
《废柴联盟》第二季将于9月23日周四在NBC首播